At night, a sound leaves
me unable to sleep.
There seems to be more
stray cats and dogs now.
Grandfather went for a
walk and has yet to return.
The nearby forest suddenly fell silent.
For a few days now,
the livestock have been afraid of
something and it's affecting their health.
It seems to be happening
all over the place.
Wait
That's similar to what happened
in the Forest of the Beast?
If the enemy has already encroached
this deep into the country!
All who use Search and Uncover!
You need to form a network and
dispatch to these areas now!
Also, call on the Six Sovereigns!
This is urgent!
All of them? Really?
Yes! Hurry! Do it now!
Why did I not take notice of this earlier?
What is this are those
bastards of the magical
empire really going
this far what did we do
to provoke such actions
do they really want
into the dungeons so
badly they resort to this
countless lives will be
caught in the light of fire
it's as if their only
desire their only purpose
is coming into our
realm just to destroy it
Thank you.
It's a good thing we got a
little money in the end, huh?
You got that right.
Good grief.
I guess I'll do you a favor then.
What's this?
It's in celebration of your first hunt.
Go on now, take it.
Are you sure?
Yeah, yeah, don't worry about it.
One goblin only gets you so much anyways.
Food somehow tastes better
after taking on a mission.
Sure does.
Okay, so how long is this girl
going to be sticking around?
Her folks must be worried sick about her.
Thanks so much for the meal.
Now then, I think I'll head back to my
home for the day and check on a few things.
Oh, great.
Is that okay?
Instructor? Of course.
That's quite all right.
You were a really big help today.
Please I absolutely look forward to assisting
you again as long as you'll have me.
I've been looking everywhere for you Lynn
Rain
Sir nor
Sorry for the sudden request,
but would you do me the
service of taking my
sister to the Mountain
District tomorrow morning,
huh?
Me I can give you a
carriage and an escort.
I'm sorry I'm not able to give
you any more details right now,
but it would be of great help to me.
I see.
Sounds like I'll need to
pack up for this journey.
We will pay you well
and cover your expenses.
Please sir, you are the only
person I can trust with this task.
And here we are, taking on
a quest through the guild.
Master said to kick back and relax
while on the way there, and well,
that sounds like a
pretty sweet deal to me.
But to be honest,
the real reason I accepted the task is
because I've never been on a carriage before,
and I wanted to see what it's like.
For somebody like me, who's
never really left the capital,
this is all the payment I could ever need.
And if I'm lucky, I'll be able to go
to a bunch of other countries too.
What's up, Lin?
Don't you want to see the scenery?
I mean, it's just about
time for the wheat harvest.
We sure do live in a
land of plenty, don't we?
Uh, okay.
One day, I want to become a normal
adventurer and do these journeys on my own.
I'm sorry my brother dropped this
request on you all of a sudden.
Ah, don't worry about it.
I am getting paid for coming along,
and I owe you for the goblin
hunt we just did anyway.
First things first,
you will travel northwest
of the capital via
carriage towards the
mountain district of Tauros.
There, I need you to just
sit tight for a while.
After that, but only if
everything seems to be copacetic,
you'll cross the mountain to
the holy theocracy of Mithra.
Are you really okay with me just
sort of coming along for the ride?
Think of it as like a vacation.
That is, if nothing happens.
I hope that everyone back home is
going to be okay while we're away.
Don't worry.
They'll be fine.
This is all just part of the plan.
What was that?
Prince himself told me to
keep my orders a secret.
In the near future, the capital
will fall into unprecedented crisis.
Should you receive report of
its destruction, at that time,
take Lin and together with Ser Noir
flee to Mithra as quietly as possible.
Does Lady Lindbergh know of this, sir?
She does not.
If I were to tell her, she would
surely refuse and stay behind.
But if there's an emergency, I
will be nowhere near the castle.
This is of utmost importance.
You are the only one I
can trust with this task.
Ines, it is your duty to
get her somewhere safe.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, your highness.
I'm sorry.
Hmm?
I must apologize that you've
become caught up in this.
You make a simple trip sound so serious.
And I gotta say, you haven't
been looking too well.
Are you sure you're feeling okay?
I'm just a little troubled by something.
But keeping you safe is another
one of my responsibilities.
You need not worry.
Thanks, but I'm not really
worried about anything.
I'm sure I can protect
myself if something comes up.
And can always run away if I need to.
You won't need to do that. Oh.
I have a shield.
I can protect you.
You have a shield?
But where is it?
I haven't seen you carrying anything.
In my case, I don't
need something to carry.
In fact, it's better in many
ways if I have nothing. Huh?
It will be easier if I just show you.
Now, Divine Shield!
Whoa!
That's amazing!
I've never seen anything like it.
Listen, if anything happens to us, hide
yourself behind this barricade of light.
Neither weapons nor magic can get through.
Yeah, sure thing.
Don't have to tell me twice.
According to Lin,
the guy with the spear who let me
train with him at the practice grounds.
I think it was Gil? Phil?
No, Armadil?
Anyway, he's so great, he was able to
bring down a dragon all on his own.
And she is no less powerful than he is.
They're on a whole
different level than me.
I get into trouble with
just a single goblin.
That is a remarkable talent. Seriously.
Talent, huh?
Shortly after being
taken into an orphanage,
I noticed there was a mysterious
power growing within me.
Inus, what's that thing?
It sure is pretty!
Ow!
He caught me!
Someone, call Director Save!
I healed her, so you need
not worry anymore, my dear.
Now, show me the power
you were using earlier.
You have a gift that has been
given to you from the heavens.
A gift?
And a historically rare one at that.
It could become a sharpened
blade able to cut anyone down,
or even a shield to protect
against adversaries.
Depending on how you use it, it could
even annihilate an entire country.
Ines, was it?
It's all right.
You can start learning
to use it beginning now.
Okay, I'm ready now!
After that, I was taken in by
the Sovereign Shield Dandog,
and I learned from the Six
Sovereigns how to use my power.
Even so, I could not quell the fear
that I would hurt someone again.
Naturally, I started to put
distance between myself and others,
and I became detached.
I drifted away from everyone.
At least, I thought I had.
I would like to have your
name, if you don't mind.
I'm Noor.
Noor!
I knew that name very well.
Never get distracted.
Dandalg was my foster father, and the
instructor I held in the highest regard.
He was always teaching me, and
I heard that name from him.
It never seems to end, does it?
The onslaught shows no sign of relenting.
Yes, I fear the soldiers
are beginning to fatigue.
It's heavy times like these.
I wish that Noor were still around.
That name again.
Oh, forget that. Never mind.
We must be steadfast. Come along.
Noor, someone worthy of
respect by my father.
Even though I have been right here.
My yearning for his
acknowledgement grew inside me.
I still feel it.
I am somehow still envious
of a man I have never met.
And now it's gotten worse, ever
since he appeared before me.
But no.
No, I cannot allow my
feelings to cloud my judgment.
I am the shield of the Clay's kingdom.
I protect Lady Lindbergh
with my very life.
That is my duty.
What's that?
There's a path in the wheat fields.
But it doesn't really look right.
Sir Noor, something wrong.
I don't know.
I thought I saw something strange
over there cutting through the field.
Stop, Inez!
I'm coming!
So it begins.
Reporting in!
Several beasts have
appeared around the capital.
The Warrior Corps are handling it, but we
don't have enough soldiers for them all.
Have the Swordsman Company block the
roads immediately to fend them off.
Instruct that all citizens
be evacuated. Also,
tell the Secret Corps and the
Hunter Corps to send as many as
possible to fight the Monster Horde
and help stave off casualties.
Do not allow a single
citizen to fall. Right.
That damned Eridus.
There will come a day in your future
when you shall regret those words.
He has finally come to make good on
his threats he boasted about, has he?
I'm afraid this is just the beginning.
I do not believe it will end with this.
Suppose not.
The Sovereigns?
We have dispatched them all.
Monsters have been seen
in various locations.
And at each one, we had
no choice but to engage.
Defend this place at all costs!
Don't leave a single one alive!
Our forces have been spread thin.
That's unfortunate.
Yes.
But Lin is safe.
She should be deep within
the mountains by now.
I have to kill them all.
No, I don't believe it.
A black death dragon.
Why is such a vicious
creature in a place like this?
Hold on!
That's...
Fairy!
Did you not notice?
We did not see that boy
in the field before.
It was only when you used your
Uncover skill that he appeared,
along with the Black Death Dragon.
You mean that kid is...
Demon folk?
Yes.
You've heard of them, haven't you?
I have.
They appear to be the same as humans,
but they are demi-humans
who have the special
ability of establishing a
mental bond with monsters.
If anything,
they are closer to beasts
than they are with humans,
and they are considered
aberrations and dangerous.
There are records from 200 years ago
when the holy theocracy of Mithra
was almost wiped out by demihumans who
were manipulating powerful monsters.
Because of that, the demon folk have
been continuously hunted by humans.
They were thought to be extinct.
Well, now it would appear some of
their descendants are still around.
If that's the case,
then of course they must hold some intense
hatred towards humans
for their eradication.
So the boy must have manipulated
the dragon to follow him here!
That is a species which
dwells in the marshlands.
They're not known to go where humans live.
It is unheard of.
Meaning clearly that boy
intends to lead that monster to
the royal capital and do harm
to the citizens of our kingdom.
It must have been the shock
of being exposed by Uncover
that caused the boy to lose
his mental hold on the dragon.
Why would Nord do that?
Why protect someone like that?
It's foolish.
Very foolish.
What on earth is that man doing?
What is he even thinking?
Whatever it is, let's help him out.
Wait, right there!
We cannot help. Nor right now.
He's on his own with this.
This frog it's not so powerful
and moves kind of slow.
That goblin was way tougher than this.
If I can just hold on until Lynn and
Ines get here, we can take it out. Oh!
If I jump out of the way,
the kid will get hit.
What is this?
No more!
That liquid right there is
the true horror of the dragon.
It's poison.
A deadly one at that.
My head is spinning.
I'm losing control of myself.
Inez was trying to say something.
She must have been trying to tell
me that this is no ordinary frog.
It brings nothing but
ruin to all in its path.
A special kind of death.
Instructor Narl!
You mustn't go.
A poisonous mist will come next.
Please let me go to him! I can't.
My duty is to protect you.
You're staying here.
If I can hold back its attacks from here
somehow, at least the princess can escape.
The kingdom needs her to survive.
Please understand, the very existence of
the kingdom is at stake here. What in this?
Princess, you need to understand.
One breath of that noxious
gas would be fatal.
Even if Sovereign Healers saying we're
here, you might not recover. No way!
Here it is!
Quick, get behind me!
So for now, you just need
to make sure you survive!
Purify!
The purification won't make it in time!
Instructor!
Sir Noor, I am sorry.
I am but a mere soldier.
I chose this path because of my
admiration for Shield Sovereign Dandal.
When I see someone in the teeth of
danger, I want to protect them, but now...
That's impossible!
Still?
In that condition?
It's heavy times like these.
I wish that Noor were still around.
Who is this man anyway?
He isn't being foolish.
He's exactly the type of person I've
always looked up to and sought out.
Doing whatever you can to protect someone,
even if you must sacrifice yourself.
A true shield!
But I thought...
I heard he was...
Okay then, I think I can
make this work out after all.
Thank you so much for watching.
Master's You can't see anything.
You can't reach it.
I'll tell you. I can't see
anything. I'll show you.
I'll give you what you're trying to.
You won't keep it.
I'll give you the chance.
We'll be
right back.